Association on American Indian Affairs Records, 1851-2016 (bulk 1922-1995): Finding Aid MC147
Public Policy Papers
- Series 10: January 2008 Addition, 1960-2006; 6 boxes
  - Tax Information, 2003; 1 box (Box 476)
  - Legal Fee, 2003; 1 box (Box 476)
  - Auditor Materials, 2003; 1 box (Box 476)
  - Return of Organization Exempt From Income Tax, 2003; 1 box (Box 476)
  - Oversized Materials, 1960-1969; 2 boxes
    - Photographs of Native Americans and Their Communities, 1960-1969; 2 boxes
      - Mounted on Board, 1960s; 1 box (Box 477)
      - Lamenated, 1960s; 1 box (Box 478)
- Series 11: February 2009 Addition, 1990 May-2008; 5 boxes
  ML.2009.004
  Series 11: February 2009 Addition (1996-2008) includes board packets and correspondence, staff minutes, state registration forms, tax-exempt certifications, scholarship information, summer camp reports, complaints and inquiries, travel files, and case files.
  Scholarship materials in Series 11 are closed for a period of 75 years from the date of their creation. All other records in this series are closed for a period of 15 years from the date of their creation.
  - Fall Board Packets, 2006-2008; 1 box (Box 479)
  - Summer Board Packets, 2006; 2008; 1 box (Box 479)
  - Spring Board Packets, 2007-2008; 1 box (Box 479)
  - State Registrations, 2005-2008; 1 box (Box 479)
  - 2006 State Form 990 Return of Organizations Exempt from Income Tax, 1 box (Box 479)
  - 2007 State Form 990 Return of Organizations Exempt from Income Tax, 1 box (Box 479)
  - Staff Call Minutes, 2002-2006; 1 box (Box 480)
  - Scholarships-Hesemeyer-Discontinued, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 480)
  - Summer Camp Reports, 2003-2008; 1 box (Box 480)
  - Complaints, Inquiries, 2002; 2007-2008; 1 box (Box 480)
  - Native American Grave/Burial Protection Act 1990 May (S. HRQ 101-952), 1 box (Box 480)
  - Travel, 2006-2007; 1 box (Box 480)
  - Data Management, 2006; 1 box (Box 480)
  - Thurman, Comes, Foley, 2005-2007; 1 box (Box 480)
  - Lewis Perkiss Communication, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 480)
  - William Means Case, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 480)
  - Hannasam McGhie Case, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 480)
  - Mending the Circle, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 480)
  - Displaced Homemaker, 2006-2007; 1 box (Box 481)
  - Emergency Aid, 2006-2007; 1 box (Box 481)
  - Asche, 2006-2007; 1 box (Box 481)
  - Young, 2006-2007; 1 box (Box 481)
  - Sequoyah, 2006-2007; 1 box (Box 557)
  - Slagle, 2006-2007; 1 box (Box 557)
  - Van Pelt, 2004-2005; 1 box (Box 557)
  - Van Pelt, 2006-2007; 1 box (Box 557)
  - Van Pelt, 2003-2004; 1 box (Box 557)
  - Hesemeyer Grade, 2006-2007; 1 box (Box 481)
  - Board Meetings and Correspondence, 1996-2001; 1 box (Box 482)
- Series 12: Febrary 2011 Addition, 1976-2016; 12 boxes
  ML.2011.005
  Series 12: February 2011 addition includes board packets (2008-2010), the 2009 annual report, newsletters 163-168, records from the Wyoming Sawmills case, sacred lands/Medicine Wheel records, and the records of scholarship recipients (2007-2009).
  Scholarship files in Subseries C are closed for a period of 75 years from the date of their creation. All other records in this series are closed for a period of 15 years from the date of their creation.
  - Subseries 12A, Wyoming Sawmills Case, 1976-2005; 5 boxes
    The materials in this subseries include many forms of legal documents and records from the Wyoming Sawmills case, including appendices to case reports, notices, motions, pleadings, petitions, statements, briefings, writs, decisions, and correspondence.
    The order in which these materials were sent to Princeton has been maintained.
    - Wyoming Sawmills v. US Forest Servoce Plaintiff-Appellant Appendix, 1987-2001; 1 box (Box 488)
      No folder.
    - Wyoming Sawmills v. US Forest Service Plaintiff-Appellant Appendix, 1987-2001; 1 box (Box 488)
    - Wyoming Sawmills v. US Forest Service Plaintiff-Appellant Appendix, 1987-2001; 1 box (Box 488)
    - Wyoming Sawmills v. US Forest Service Plaintiff-Appellant Appendix, 1987-2001; 1 box (Box 488)
    - Wyoming Sawmills v. US Forest Service Motion to Dismiss Documents, 1999; 1 box (Box 488)
    - WYSM Decision, 2004; 1 box (Box 488)
    - Notices/Motions, 2001-2003; 1 box (Box 488)
    - Pleadings, 1999-2004; 1 box (Box 488)
    - WY SM Notes, 2002; 1 box (Box 488)
    - Notes: WYSM Argument 5/6/03, 2003 May 6; 1 box (Box 488)
    - Wyoming Sawmills v. US Forest Service Transcript of Administrative Hearing Proceedings, 1999; 1 box (Box 488)
    - Wyoming Sawmills v. US Forest Service Plaintiff's Opening Brief, 1999; 1 box (Box 488)
    - Wyoming Sawmills v. US Forest Service Plaintiff's Reply Brief, 1999 October; 1 box (Box 488)
    - WY/SM Brief of Intervenor Appellee, 2002; 1 box (Box 488)
    - Misc. Cover Letters, 2002; 1 box (Box 488)
    - Correspondence, 2000-2005; 1 box (Box 488)
    - Certificate of Appearance/Certificate of Service/Transcript Form/Docket Statements, 2002; 1 box (Box 488)
    - Affidavit: Harding Declaration: Myers, 1988-1996; 1 box (Box 488)
    - WYSM - Writ of Certiorari - Brier for Respondents in Opposition, 2005; 1 box (Box 488)
    - WYSM - On Petition for Writ of Certiorari to the US Court of Appeals for the 10th Circuit Supreme Court, 2005; 1 box (Box 488)
    - WYSM - Writ of Certiorari - Opposition to Petition for Writ of Certiorari, 2005; 1 box (Box 488)
    - Sage Council, 2004; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Certificate of Service, 1999; 1 box (Box 483)
    - MW Record Index, 2002; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Volume I, 1991; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Volume II, 1991; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Volume II, 1991; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Volume III, 1991; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Volume I, 1991; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Volume III, 1991-1992; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Volume IV, 1992; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Volume IV, 1992; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Volume IV, 1992-1993; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Volume V, 1993; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Volume V, 1993; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Volume VI, 1993; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Volume VI, 1993-1994; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Volume VII, 1994; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Volume VII, 1995; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Volume III, 1996; 1 box (Box 483)
    - Volume XIV, 1993; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Volume XIV, 1993; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Volume XV, 1994; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Volume XV, 1994-1999; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Volume XIV, 1991-1993; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Volume XII, 1976-1980; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Volume XIV, 1976-1980; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Volume XII, 1978-1980; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Volume XII, 1994-1997; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Volume XIII, 1994; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Volume X, 1993-1995; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Volume X, 1998; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Volume X, 1997; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Volume X, 1996; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Volume X, 1995; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Volume XII, 1996-1997; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Volume IX, 1996-1997; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Volume IX, 1996; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Volume III, 1996; 1 box (Box 484)
    - Appellees' Answering Brief, 2003; 1 box (Box 489)
    - Appellees' Opening Brief, 2003; 1 box (Box 489)
    - On Appeal From the United States District Court for the District of Oregon: Supplemental Excerpt of Record, 2003; 1 box (Box 489)
  - Subseries 12B, Sacred Lands, 1990-2010; 4 boxes
    The materials in this subseries include records of the Sacred Lands Protection Coalition as well as legislative and regulatory records related to sacred lands issues. Also included are a variety of records of meetings of groups or organizations addressing sacred lands issues (e.g., the Medicine Wheel Coalition). These include reports various landmarks, sites, and plans. In addition there are some brochures, newsletters, and newsclippings on sacred lands issues.
    - Sacred Lands Protection Coalition, 2002; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Sacred Lands Protection Coalition, 2002; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Circle of Sacred Smoke, 2008; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Day of Prayer 2003, 1 box (Box 485)
    - In the Light of Reverence, 2002-2005; 1 box (Box 485)
    - ABA Env Conf. - Sacred Lands Pre Slnt at.on Sept 2008, 1 box (Box 485)
    - NHPA - Legislative, 2006; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Proposed NHPA Regs, 2002-2006; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Sh Outreach, 2003; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Sacred Lands 2001, 2002; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Sacred Sites 2001, 2001-2002; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Misc. SL Post 2004, 2006-2010; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Forest Service Training: Cultural Reservation Law May 2003, 2003 May; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Ford Training Development 03, 2003-2004; 1 box (Box 485)
    - SLPP Brochure - Ordering Info, 2003; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Sacred Places Quarterly Reports Guy Lopez, 2003 April; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Guy's SL Stuff He Brough - Site Specific, 2003; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Environmental Justice (Guy), 2003-2004; 1 box (Box 485)
    - VLS Legal, 2002-2003; 1 box (Box 485)
    - MISC. Advocacy, 2004; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Reports from Dean Sugee, 2003 March 10; 1 box (Box 485)
    - SL Pro Bono, 2003; 1 box (Box 485)
    - 2003 Rapid City Lawyer's Brainstorm Session, 2003 May; 1 box (Box 485)
    - 2004 CA WS, Trad. Know, Envir. Just., SL, 1 box (Box 485)
    - Harvard - 2004, 2004 January; 1 box (Box 485)
    - ABA Writing Competition, 2004; 1 box (Box 485)
    - Telecommunications Initiative, 2006; 1 box (Box 486)
    - BLM Miscellaneous, 2005; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Cherokee Nat. of OK v Norton (Delaware Tribe), 2005; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Cave Rock, 2004-2007; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Cave Rock, 2000-2003; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Black Horse Return, 2002 November; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Big Tesuque Sacred Site, 2001 August; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Nevada Revised Statutes, 2002 December; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Navajo Uranium Mining, 2005-2007; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Mount Graham, 2002-2006; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Montana DEQ, 2003 August; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Missouri River MOA, 2002-2003; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Little Big Horn, 2003 June; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Projects/Gwich'in/Caribou Herd, 2001; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Gonzales v. O Centro Espirita Beneficiate, 2005; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Glen Canyon Dam Adaptive Management Program, 2002 October 22; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Apache Survival Coalition, 2005 March 28; 1 box (Box 486)
    - D, M & E RR Project, 2003 September; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Pipetone Meeting 2002 (Jan), 2002-2003; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Port Angeles/Lower Elwah, 2004 December; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Quechan Sacred Site 08443-001, 1999-2002; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Pipestone - NFS Book 2007, 1 box (Box 486)
    - Paseo del Norte (Petroglyph), 2004-2005; 1 box (Box 486)
    - SAGE Council, 2005; 1 box (Box 486)
    - OTERG Mesa, 2005-2006; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Western Shoshone, 2002; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Shoshone Sundance Permit, 2000-2002; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Sandia Pueblo Land Claim, 2002; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Sand Creek Massacre Site, 2001-2008; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Weatherman's Draw Sacred Site, 2001; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Snoqualmie Falls, 2002-2006; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Draft of Book: Working in Indian Country, 2010; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Justice, 2008; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Sharon Franklet Environmental Leadership, 2009 March; 1 box (Box 486)
    - ACHP/Advisory Council, 2003-2006; 1 box (Box 486)
    - ACHP Draft Policy Statement on Human Resources, 2005-2007; 1 box (Box 486)
    - ACHP: Section 106 Revisions, 1997; 1 box (Box 486)
    - SS Legal Protection Reference ACHP, 2006; 1 box (Box 486)
    - National Trust/Historic Preservation, 2005-2006; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Big Horn Nat. Forest Plan Revision, 2003; 1 box (Box 486)
    - JT Evergreen Article 12/05 SL & Forest Man: Rel. Freedom Accomodations, 2004-2005; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Coalitions for the Free Exercise of Religion, 1997-1999; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Cutter v. Wilkinson (RLUIPA) Rel. Free Constitutionality, 2004-2005; 1 box (Box 486)
    - National Native American Prisoner's Rights Advocacy Coalition, 1995-1999; 1 box (Box 486)
    - Ceremonies on Open Space Land, 2002-2004; 1 box (Box 486)
    - AIRFA Oversight Hearing 7/14/04, 2004 July 14; 1 box (Box 486)
    - November 2002 Sacred Lands Conference, 1 box (Box 486)
    - Sacred Site Land Forum - Boulder?Denver October 2001, 2001-2002; 1 box (Box 486)
    - 2003 Participant Contact List, 2003-2004; 1 box (Box 487)
    - 2003 Summit Travol, 2003-2004; 1 box (Box 487)
    - 2003 Federal-Tribal Summit On-Site Registration, 1 box (Box 487)
    - 2003 Federal-Tribal Summit Pre-Registered Attendees, 2003-2004; 1 box (Box 487)
    - 2003 Summit Contracts/Invoice, 1 box (Box 487)
    - Summit Materials - 2003, 1 box (Box 487)
    - Misc. Summit Planning, 2003-2004; 1 box (Box 487)
    - Jack's PowerPoints 9/04, 2004 September; 1 box (Box 487)
    - Sacred Places Workshop 2005, 1 box (Box 487)
    - Sacred Places Workshop 2004, 2004 September; 1 box (Box 487)
    - Sacred Lands Legal Workshop Sept. 22, 2004, 2003-2004; 1 box (Box 487)
    - Participants/Evaluations Sept. 22, 2004, 1 box (Box 487)
    - SLP Legal Workshop Forms, 2004 September; 1 box (Box 487)
    - May 2005 SLLWS, Redding, CA, 1 box (Box 487)
    - May 2005 SLLWS Funding, 1 box (Box 487)
    - List of Policies by Department/Agency 9/04, 2003 July; 1 box (Box 487)
    - Practical Advice for Tribal Advocates 9/04, 2004; 1 box (Box 487)
    - Sacred Lands Training Moa, 2006; 1 box (Box 487)
    - SLP Attendees, Feb. 2008, 1 box (Box 487)
    - Evaluations, 2005; 1 box (Box 487)
    - Attendees - May, 2005, 2004-2005; 1 box (Box 487)
    - Appendix, 2004; 1 box (Box 487)
    - Generic Cover Sheets, undated; 1 box (Box 487)
    - Handouts, 2005 May; 1 box (Box 487)
    - Changes to May 2005 BLM, 1 box (Box 487)
    - Tribal Energy Resource Agreements, 2006; 1 box (Box 487)
    - Sacred Lands Religious Freedom, 1991 May; 1 box (Box 487)
    - HSET - Feb 2006, 2006 February; 1 box (Box 487)
    - 2008 OSET, 1 box (Box 487)
    - Sacred Lands Training Materials, 2006; 1 box (Box 487)
    - Monique Fordham - Other, 2003-2004; 1 box (Box 487)
    - Larry Keown Materials, 1999-2003; 1 box (Box 487)
    - SL Fundraising Proposals, 2005; 1 box (Box 487)
    - Miscellaneous (Sacred Lands), 2006-2010; 1 box (Box 487)
    - BLM Proposed Rules on Land Withdrawals, 2008 October; 1 box (Box 487)
    - Rocky Mtn. Mineral Law Institute 2008, 1 box (Box 487)
    - CARA, 2001; 1 box (Box 487)
    - Medicine Wheel By-laws - Sacred Sites Brochure, 1990; 1 box (Box 490)
    - MWC Corporate Issues, 2004-2005; 1 box (Box 490)
    - Newspaper: Arizona Native Scene, 2005 January; 1 box (Box 490)
    - Medicine Wheel Coalition Addresses, 2001; 1 box (Box 490)
    - Historic Preservation Plan (HPP) for the Medicine Wheel National Historic Landmark and Vicinity, 1996; 1 box (Box 490)
    - AAIA Administration - Monitoring, 1993; 1 box (Box 490)
    - MWC Resolution May 2005, 2005 May; 1 box (Box 490)
    - Post S and T - MLUC (non-MW) Materials, 1999-2003; 1 box (Box 490)
    - News Articles, 2000-2005; 1 folder (Box 490)
    - Post S&T Non MW-MW, 2003-2006; 1 box (Box 490)
    - MWC 2004, 1 box (Box 490)
    - Annual Medicine Wheel Meeting, 2005 December; 1 box (Box 490)
    - MW Misc 2005, 1 box (Box 490)
    - MWC, 2005-2008; 1 box (Box 490)
    - MWR 2008, 1 box (Box 490)
    - Post 2003 MW, 2003-2005; 1 box (Box 490)
    - MW Reports - 1994, 1999, 2000, 2001, 1994-2002; 1 box (Box 490)
    - Medicine Wheel Report 2007, 2003-2007; 1 box (Box 490)
  - Subseries 12C, Scholarships, 2003-2010; 3 boxes
    This subseries includes the records of the various AAIA scholarship recipients.
    The order in which these materials were sent to Princeton has been maintained. The records are grouped by the name of the scholarship (e.g., Van Pelt) for a particular time period, though they are not in chronological order. Within each type of scholarship group the files are labeled with the name of the recipient for that year.
    - Jacob Keyes: Young 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Jonathan Tsosie: Young 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Joshua Zunie: Young 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Julie Benns: Hesemeyer 2006-2007, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Jamie Dressler: Hesemeyer 2006-2007, 2006-2008; 1 box (Box 491)
    - Frechette, Brandon, 2003-2008; 1 box (Box 491)
    - Hernandez, Joshua, 2003-2008; 1 box (Box 491)
    - Chelsay Jimmie, 2003-2008; 1 box (Box 491)
    - Sherry King: Hesemeyer 2006-2007, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Danielle Scotti: 2004-2005 Hesemeyer, 2004-2008; 1 box (Box 491)
    - Carla Palmer: Hesemeyer 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Trudi Reyes: Hesemeyer 2006-2007, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Noelle Garcia: Hesemeyer 2006-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Gary Baldwin: Van Pelt 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Tasia Martinez: Van Pelt 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Stefani Sager: Van Pelt 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Ashley Aguilar: Van Pelt 2006-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Scott Atole: Van Pelt 2006-2008, 2005-2008; 1 box (Box 491)
    - Reba Begay: Van Pelt 2004-2005, 2004-2008; 1 box (Box 491)
    - Arrol Perry: Van Pelt 2006-2007, 2006-2008; 1 box (Box 491)
    - Tyler Rolette: Van Pelt 2006-2007, 2006-2008; 1 box (Box 491)
    - Vanessa Scholfield: Van Pelt 2006-2007, 2006-2008; 1 box (Box 491)
    - Zane Whyte: Van Pelt 2005-2006, 2005-2008; 1 box (Box 491)
    - Ann Braun: Emergency - Spring 2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Marissa Eagleman: Emergency - Oct. 2007, 2007-2008; 1 box (Box 491)
    - Owen McCurdy Emergency Spring 2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Doneen Marissa Emergency Sp. 2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Myrna Whitetail Emergency Spring 2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Melissa Kari Displaced 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Clarice Madalena Displaced 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Bambi Rodriguez Displaced 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Shanna Williams-Thom, 2007-2008; 1 box (Box 491)
    - Jodi Abbott Sequoyah 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - John Caudillo Sequoyah 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Ann Douglas Sequoyah 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Brendan Fourbanks Sequoyah 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Ki-shan Lara Sequoyah 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Dave Scott Sequoyah 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Carly Tex Sequoyah 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Fawn Wasin Zi Sequoyah 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Camille Fisher Sequoyah 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Ashley Brewington Slagle 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Eric Gant Slagle 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Courtney Lewis Slagle 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Kimberly Locklear Slagle 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Karston Smith Asche 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Julia Randall Asche 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Amanda Murphy Asche 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Rachelle Miles Asche 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Andrew McCoy Asche 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Melvina Bissonette Asche 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 491)
    - Marcia St. Goddard Sequoyah 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Crystal Allen Sequoyah 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Brendan Fourbanks Sequoyah 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Jeston Morris Sequoyah 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Jenny Patten Sequoyah 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Sasanehsaeh Pyawasay Sequoyah 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Jose Cazares Sequoyah 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - John Candillo Sequoyah 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Ki-Shan Lara Sequoyah 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Rachael Mendenhall Van Pelt 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Sara Iron Lightening Van Pelt 2006-2007, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Dina Long Knife Van Pelt 2006-2007, 2006-2008; 1 box (Box 492)
    - Jason Rood Van Pelt 2005-2006, 2005-2009; 1 box (Box 492)
    - Fanaye Barney 2004-2005 Van Pelt, 2004-2009; 1 box (Box 492)
    - Walter Beaver Van Pelt 2005-2006, 2005-2009; 1 box (Box 492)
    - Rebekah Jarvey Van Pelt 2006-2007, 2006-2009; 1 box (Box 492)
    - Cedar Kakkak Van Pelt 2006-2007, 2006-2009; 1 box (Box 492)
    - Michelle Swallow Van Pelt 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Dallas Boyd Van Pelt 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Lucinda Montross Van Pelt 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Donald Richardson Van Pelt 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Adriana Wahwasuek Van Pelt 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Lucas Tyree Slagle 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Erica Hunt Slagle 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Joshua Locklear Slagle 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Tala Smith Slagle 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Norma Castro Displaced 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Michael S. Fox Displaced 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Cecelia Grant Displaced 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Richard Gray Displaced 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Delphine Dan Displaced 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Gentri White Young 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Zellisha Quam Young 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Lonie Wright Young 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Cindy DuBray Emergency Aid Jan 2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Rachelle Miles Emergency Spring 2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Natane Runningfox Emergency Aid Spring 2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Edie Cook Twite Emergency Aid Jan 2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Melissa Cuney Blacksmith Emergency Fall 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Clifford Stone Emergency Aid Fall 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Brooke Swaney Emergency Aid Dec 2008, 2008-2009; 1 box (Box 492)
    - Kenneth Richards Emergency Aid F2008, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Aaron Sparks Hesemeyer 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Katherine Hubbard Hesemeyer 2006-2007, 2006-2009; 1 box (Box 492)
    - Andrea Anspach 2004-2005 Hesemeyer, 2004-2009; 1 box (Box 492)
    - Patricia Kimmerly 2004-2005 Hesemeyer, 2004-2008; 1 box (Box 492)
    - Cecelia Harrington Hesemeyer 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Olin Bekis Hesemeyer 2007-2008, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Zachary Beaver Hesemeyer 2007-2008, 2007-2009; 1 box (Box 492)
    - Rhea Allery Asche 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Samuel Cason Asche 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Rachael Ray Asche 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Jeanna Spannring Asche 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Crystal Tulley Asche 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Sharon Yazzie Asche 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 492)
    - Adam Dell Van Pelt 2006-2007, 2006-2010; 1 box (Box 493)
    - Tabitha Gordon Van Pelt 2006-2007, 2006-2010; 1 box (Box 493)
    - Corey Gardipee, 2006-2010; 1 box (Box 493)
    - Nathan Lorts Hesemeyer 2008-2009, 2008-2010; 1 box (Box 493)
    - Connie Sankwich Hesemeyer 2009-2010, 1 box (Box 493)
    - Darrow Peynesta Hesemeyer 2008-2009, 2008-2010; 1 box (Box 493)
    - Jeffrey Omidvaran Hesemeyer 2009-2010, 1 box (Box 493)
    - Daniel Concho 2004-2005 Hesemeyer, 2004-2010; 1 box (Box 493)
    - R'nld Wheeler Hesemeyer 2006-2007, 2006-2010; 1 box (Box 493)
    - Terra Branson Hesemeyer 2006-2007, 2006-2010; 1 box (Box 493)
    - Derek Fiddler Hesemeyer 2008-2009, 1 box (Box 493)
    - Christine Adam Hesemeyer 2004-2005, 2004-2009; 1 box (Box 493)
    - Marlis Luke Hesemeyer 2008-2009, 2008-2010; 1 box (Box 493)
    - Melissa Colby Sequoyah 2009-2010, 1 box (Box 493)
    - Matthew Gilbert Sequoyah 2009-2010, 1 box (Box 493)
    - Brian Hoeffner Sequoyah 2009-2010, 1 box (Box 493)
    - Delitha Livingston, 2009-2010; 1 box (Box 493)
    - Cody McCullough Sequoyah 2009-2010, 1 box (Box 493)
    - Michelle Parkin Sequoyah 2009-2010, 1 box (Box 493)
    - Danielle Swanson Sequoyah 2009-2010, 1 box (Box 493)
    - Karen Malone Sequoyah 2009-2010, 1 box (Box 493)
    - Fern Wesley Displaced 2009-2010, 1 box (Box 493)
    - Glenda Loretto Displaced 2009-2010, 1 box (Box 493)
    - Candy DuBray Displaced 2009-2010, 1 box (Box 493)
    - Patricia Fields Displaced 2009-2010, 1 box (Box 493)
    - Darlene Lee Displaced 2009-2010, 1 box (Box 493)
    - Richard Gray Displaced 2009-2010, 1 box (Box 493)
    - Christopher Cordts Emergency Feb. 2009-2010, 1 box (Box 493)
    - Charla White Eagle Emergency Spring 2010, 1 box (Box 493)
    - Raelene Zospah Emergency June 2010, 1 box (Box 493)